<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Cat's Cradle Events</title>
    <link>https://catscradle.com/events/</link>
    <description>Upcoming events at Cat's Cradle music venues</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:15:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dogpark (Friday, March 13 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/dogpark/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/dogpark/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Friday, March 13 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 22:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grace Ives (Sunday, May 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/grace-ives/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/grace-ives/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, May 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Facebook<br/>Instagram<br/>TikTok<br/>Spotify]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut Worms (Saturday, April 18 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/cut-worms/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/cut-worms/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Saturday, April 18 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Motorco Music Hall<br/><br/>Website<br/>Instagram<br/>YouTube<br/>Spotify<br/>Facebook<br/>TikTok]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Pears and Together Pangea (Monday, April 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-red-pears-and-together-pangea/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-red-pears-and-together-pangea/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Monday, April 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Motorco Music Hall]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Bochner (Sunday, March 08 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/rachel-bochner/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/rachel-bochner/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, March 08 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aterciopelados (Tuesday, March 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/aterciopelados-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/aterciopelados-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[An Evening With<br/><br/>Tuesday, March 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tigers Jaw (Wednesday, April 08 - Doors: 6 pm : Show: 7 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/tigers-jaw-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/tigers-jaw-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Hot Flash Heat Wave, Creeks (solo)<br/><br/>Wednesday, April 08 - Doors: 6 pm : Show: 7 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cass McCombs (Tuesday, May 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/cass-mccombs/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/cass-mccombs/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuesday, May 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>Over the past twenty plus years, Cass McCombs has journeyed a singular path as an uncompromising song-carver, guitarist and singer.<br/>Along with the finest squadron of collaborators and bandmates, his music travels gracefully over seemingly contradictory terrain, from infectious guitar riffage to intensely personal lyricism.<br/>In August 2025, Cass released his newest album “Interior Live Oak” to rave reviews including 5 stars from the Guardian, an 8.1 from Pitchfork who said “16 songs and not a throwaway among them…,” a 9/10 from Uncut Magazine, and a rave from Mojo magazine who said “…this is the kind of record it’s impossible to be casual about.”<br/>Interior Live Oak is his most personal album to date, and, more than any previous record, shows his vast range as a lyricist and musician. It draws from everything Cass has created over two decades of experimentation to cut through with a direct and clarifying light.<br/>Cass McCombs will embark on his “Interior Live Oak Live” tour over 2026. He lives in New York City.<br/>Website | Facebook | Instagram | Soundcloud | Spotify]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrboro Bluegrass Festival Presents Bluegrass In The Backroom (Wednesday, February 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/carrboro-bluegrass-festival-presents-bluegrass-in-the-backroom-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/carrboro-bluegrass-festival-presents-bluegrass-in-the-backroom-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Seated Show<br/><br/>Wednesday, February 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Jennings (Friday, March 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/mason-jennings/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/mason-jennings/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Seated Show<br/><br/>Friday, March 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>This is a seated show.<br/>Minneapolis songwriter Mason Jennings shares his new video for the single, “Only Lovers Welcome” from his brand new album, Underneath The Roses out now via Loosegroove Records. Underneath The Roses is available on limited-edition colored vinyl and is available here. Watch and share the video for “Only Lovers Welcome” here.<br/>Jennings writes that the songs from Underneath The Roses were, “Written in an unprecedented burst,” following the birth of his son, Western, in March 2022. Jennings explains, “I hadn’t written any songs in about a year. I had been dealing with the psychological after effects of the pandemic as well as the loss of my dad. So, when Western was born I didn’t expect to be writing much. But immediately he was responding to music in a very intense way. For this album, between May and November 2022, I wrote 48 songs! They certainly uplifted me and connected me with the creative spirit, and spirit in general, again. They cover all kinds of ground but, when I listen back, I think the central theme is overcoming fear with love.”<br/>Jennings also released a video for, “No Ordinary Friend,” which he explains, “Depicts two of the most important decisions a person can make. One, whether or not they believe in a loving higher power and two, who they decide to choose as a life long romantic partner. This song is referring to both of those and the choices I’ve made.”<br/>“Stone Gossard and Regan Hagar from Loosegroove Records helped me edit the 48 down to 11. I then enlisted the help of my Painted Shield bandmates to record the songs.”<br/>Jennings and Gossard are ongoing collaborators in the band Painted Shield, who released their 2021 debut album on Loosegroove, the influential indie label that Gossard founded back in 1994 issued records from acts such as Critters Buggin, Malfunkshun, Weapon of Choice and Devilhead, and was the launching point for Queens of the Stone Age’s debut album in 1998.<br/>Jenning’s previous album ‘Real Heart’ came out in January 2022 and received Triple/Non-comm radio across KCMP Minneapolis, WFPK Louisville, WPYA Birmingham, KRCL Salt Lake City, WMMM Madison, WQKL Ann Arbor, KCSN LA, KRVB Boise, WCLZ Portland, WDSE Duluth, WRLT Nashville, WXPN Philly, WXRV Boston, & WZEW Mobile.<br/>Press highlights include: American Songwriter, Relix, No Depression, Grateful Web, Take Effect 9/10 review, & Jam Bands<br/>Jennings adds “I called it Underneath The Roses because I feel like these songs are musical roses and when I look below them there are many thorns and so much dirt and soil. All of it was needed for them to come into existence and bloom. It’s been a long hard road of self-discovery and discernment for me the last few years and the roses wouldn’t be here without what lies underneath. Hope you enjoy the music!”<br/>Website | Spotify | Facebook | Instagram]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camping in Alaska (Monday, April 06 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/camping-in-alaska/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/camping-in-alaska/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Dead Butterflies, Stella<br/><br/>Monday, April 06 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Camping in Alaska is a post-emo band based in Huntsville, AL. Austin Davis and Jacob Stewart started writing music together at age 15, drawing from influences of childhood-favorite bands such as Jawbreaker, Modest Mouse, and Knapsack. They started their careers in Austin’s mom’s garage and soon began playing DIY shows all around North Alabama with the addition of Ben Cape and Jacob Hill. Their breakout album about being in high school and hanging out in parking lots, please be nice, was recorded in 2013 and quickly took underground internet forums by storm after the popular YouTube channel jommeez uploaded the album, their most popular song, “c u in da ballpit,” holding 1.9 million views to date. After Ben left the band, BATHE was recorded in 2014 and picked up by Broken World Media for a cassette release in 2015.<br/>The band took a hiatus for a couple of years after recording WELCOME HOME SON in 2016, a darker, more serious album about addiction and loss. With the addition of Dani Fandre, the band made a strong comeback in 2022, releasing an EP of acoustic demos recorded through 2017 and 2018 called Lost & Found and selling out both of their come-back shows.<br/>In September 2023 they released Hollow Eyes, a precursor to their next full length, drawing influence from Jawbox and The Weakerthans and grappling with more mature subject matter pertaining to addiction, homelessness and finding a way out. After the success of an almost all-sold-out Midwest and East Coast please be nice Ten Year Anniversary tour, Camping in Alaska plans to go back to the studio to record their long-awaited full length Eggbeater Jesus and hit the road again on the West Coast in 2024.<br/>Instagram | Spotify | YouTube | Bandcamp]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Braymores, echo plum (Tuesday, April 14 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-braymores-echo-plum/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-braymores-echo-plum/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuesday, April 14 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>YouTube<br/>Instagram<br/>Spotify<br/>Soundcloud<br/>TikTok]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Ramsey &amp; Carl Broemel (of My Morning Jacket) – Celestun Tour (Thursday, February 26 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/tyler-ramsey-carl-broemel-of-my-morning-jacket-celestun-tour/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/tyler-ramsey-carl-broemel-of-my-morning-jacket-celestun-tour/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Maggie Halfman<br/><br/>Thursday, February 26 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Instagram<br/>Facebook<br/>YouTube<br/>TikTok<br/>Spotify]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delicate Steve (Sunday, April 19 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/delicate-steve/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/delicate-steve/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, April 19 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melt (Friday, May 01 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/melt-3/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/melt-3/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Friday, May 01 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geordie Greep (Tuesday, June 09 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/geordie-greep/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/geordie-greep/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuesday, June 09 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>Is The New Sound a tonic for these times? Let’s ask Geordie Greep.<br/>“Music can be so much more than learning to play the same as everybody else. It can be anything you want. With recording The New Sound, it was the first time I have had no one to answer to. Being in a band (black midi), we often have this ‘we can do everything’ feeling, but you are also kind of limited in that approach, and sometimes it’s good to do something else, to let go of things.” Geordie’s debut solo album boasts a brand of high quality, all-embracing alternative pop fun not heard in a very long time, walking the line between the ridiculous and brilliant with a teflon-coated aplomb.<br/>How the record came about is a thing to marvel at. Over thirty session musicians were involved in its making, on two continents. Greep says, “Half of the tracks were done in Brazil, with local musicians pulled together at the last minute. They’d never heard anything I’d done before, they were just interested in the demos I’d made. The tracking was all done in one, maybe two days.” The spirit of Greep’s increasingly febrile and furtive soliloquies simultaneously calls to mind both Frank Zappa and Frank Sinatra, with a healthy dash of Scott Walker sprinkled throughout. The instrumental title track is a jazz-funk workout that could double as a soundtrack for a TV series or the intro music for a Broadway musical. Brass, wah-wah pedal and bass stabs, choruses and polyrhythms, all fizz and tumble around the place creating a sense of excitement and expectation. Tracks often oscillate from whispers to shouts, and start and end on a bang.<br/>The stories themselves act as a shopping list of the Active Male Imagination. A series of vignettes, where Geordie Greep plays the role of emcee and conductor. The characters we hear from are engaged in wild fantasies and situations in which they inevitably falter. “The main theme of the record is desperation; someone who is kidding themselves that they have everything under control, but they don’t.” Here Greep gives color to a set of imaginings which include cannibalism, being boiled alive, and a woman giving birth to a goat. Street life is all around The New Sound: the listener is thrown into a world of cafes, bars, rented rooms, cabarets and strange museums. Here we see our heroes carry out a series of naughty assignments, military cosplay or socio-economic triumphs. The lines between parody and sermon are often blurred. The urbane romantic fantasy of single ‘Holy Holy’ tells the story of an imaginary liaison in a nightclub, soundtracked by ’noughties indie chords and bravura Latin big band arrangements – including a three-piano attack. What next? “My plan is to ‘do a Keith Jarrett thing’, have a different group of session musicians in a different place and lean into the fact that we’re not going to get it the same.”<br/>How can anything ever be ‘the same’ with Greep at the helm?<br/>Website | Instagram]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beths (Thursday, June 18 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-beths-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-beths-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Thursday, June 18 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snail Mail (Monday, April 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/snail-mail-3/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/snail-mail-3/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Monday, April 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Haw River Ballroom<br/><br/>Website<br/>Bandcamp<br/>Facebook<br/>Instagram]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vaultboy (Sunday, April 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/vaultboy/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/vaultboy/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, April 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Instagram<br/>Soundcloud<br/>YouTube<br/>Spotify<br/>TikTok]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billie Marten (Friday, April 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/billie-marten/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/billie-marten/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Friday, April 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily Yacina (Friday, May 01 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/emily-yacina/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/emily-yacina/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Friday, May 01 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gelli Haha – Where in the World is Gelli Haha Tour 2026 (Tuesday, May 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/gelli-haha-where-in-the-world-is-gelli-haha-tour-2026/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/gelli-haha-where-in-the-world-is-gelli-haha-tour-2026/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuesday, May 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Gelli Haha exists somewhere between Studio 54 and Area 51, where dancefloors become playgrounds and cheeky aesthetics ignite imagination. A shapeshifter, a sonic acrobat, a performer with one foot in the cosmos and the other in a slapstick routine, Gelli Haha is a space for pure creative chaos.<br/>For her opening trick, Gelli Haha presents Switcheroo, the debut album via Innovative Leisure, to be released in June 2025. With a shared taste for off-kilter pop and vintage gear, producer Sean Guerin (of De Lux) joined Gelli in turning freshly-formed demos into a high-voltage experiment, abandoning meticulous structure for something freer and more electrifying. Every song on Switcheroo makes use of a myriad of recording toys; wacky analog effects, such as the Eventide Harmonizer, MXR Pitch Transposer, and various Electrix units, fashion an intentionally flawed and strictly silly texture throughout the album.<br/>Gelli Haha’s music thrives on duality: playful but profound, tongue-in-cheek but sincere. “Bounce House” is the child-like innocence; “Spit” is the S-words-only underground-club grit. “Piss Artist” revels in tequila-fueled storytelling about an infamous party moment (involving a jar — don’t ask, just dance), while “Normalize” feels like you’re stuck in Play-Doh.<br/>It’s a practice in play – recording vocals mid-jump, translating drum fills into mouth sounds, granting your best friend’s wish for a song about them. A bear attack crashes through the happy-go-lucky “Dynamite”, “Funny Music” ends with a sudden “BONK!”— because why not?<br/>The emotional rainbow stretches beyond the positive — Gelli pouts and wails on “Tiramisu”, demanding to know and feel everything, while “Pluto is not a planet it’s a restaurant” closes the album in a darker, heart-throbbing track with the repeated cry: “I’m afraid.”<br/>Switcheroo is the soundtrack to the Gelliverse, a sensory adventure sphere created by Gelli. This live revue is an invitation into a world of dolphin balloons, flutes, mini trampolines, and a stage bathed in the project’s primary color, red – bold and full of mischief.<br/>Gelli Haha isn’t foolproof. It’s by design. Switcheroo is an exercise in letting go, an inside joke turned theatrical spectacle. Participation is encouraged. Surrender is required.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivalry Night (Thursday, March 05 - Doors: 6:30 pm : Show: 7:30 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/rivalry-night-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/rivalry-night-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Dugout Entertainment Presents<br/><br/>Thursday, March 05 - Doors: 6:30 pm : Show: 7:30 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Dugout Entertainment presents Rivalry Night featuring top talent from UNC and Duke! Chapel Hill favorites Jackson Slater and Red Kanoo will be representing the Tar Heels, while Durham veterans Weekend Therapy and rising newcomers Dialtone represent the Blue Devils! This will be an exciting night of music and community, be sure to show out and wear your favorite shades of blue!<br/>Jackson Slater || UNC || Instagram Weekend Therapy || Duke || Instagram Red Kanoo || UNC || Instagram Dialtone || Duke || Instagram]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rigometrics – Rigossance Tour (Thursday, April 02 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/rigometrics-rigossance-tour/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/rigometrics-rigossance-tour/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Pollen<br/><br/>Thursday, April 02 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Rigometrics is making serious waves in the Northeast music scene with a dynamic, high-energy sound that blends the soul of classic rock with the grit of funk and blues, the hooks of indie, and the urgency of modern alternative. Their music fuses Josef Berger’s searing guitar work, Derek Haney’s hard-hitting, groove-driven drums, and Keenan Hendricks’ soaring vocals and swaggering piano, which doubles as the bass in their live setup, creating a genre-blurring style that feels both timeless and fresh. The result is a live experience and growing catalog that consistently draws in diverse audiences and fuels an ever-expanding, loyal fan base.<br/>Since forming in 2021, the three-piece has toured the East Coast and South ten times, sold out 300-cap venues, headlined major shows in Maine, and played over 350 gigs, entirely independently. Their catalog includes 2025’s Live in Maine II and single Couldn’t Tell Ya, 2024’s EP Elodie, live album Live in Maine, and singles Endless Road, All My Friends (Live for the Weekend), and No Smoke; 2023’s EP No Time to Waste and single Share the Fortune; and their 2022 debut album Rig N’ Roll. These projects are being shared through constant energetic live performances and an undeniable stage presence via a renovated school bus that the Rigometrics calls home when on the road.<br/>To bring these releases to life, Rigometrics collaborated with top-tier producers Jon Wyman, Matt Perry, and Anthony Gatti, as well as Grammy winners Dave Gutter, Adam Ayan, and ‘Bassy’ Bob Brockmann. Together, they crafted music that elevates Rigometrics’ signature sound while staying deeply rooted in the spirit of rock ‘n’ roll.<br/>LinkTree | Instagram | Spotify | TikTok | YouTube]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiss Golden Messenger – I’m People Tour (Saturday, November 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/hiss-golden-messenger-im-people-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/hiss-golden-messenger-im-people-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Saturday, November 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>here]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiss Golden Messenger – I’m People Tour (Sunday, November 22 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/hiss-golden-messenger-im-people-tour-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/hiss-golden-messenger-im-people-tour-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, November 22 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>here]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Callahan (Tuesday, May 12 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/bill-callahan/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/bill-callahan/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Tuesday, May 12 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Haw River Ballroom<br/><br/>My Days of 58 is the eighth Bill Callahan album, his first since 2022. The twelve tunes here open uncanny depths of expression as Bill continues to blaze one of the most original songwriting-and-performance trails out there. With My Days of 58, he applies the living, breathing energies of his live shows to the studio process, sharpening his slice-of-life portraiture to cut deeper than ever before.<br/>The core musicians featured on My Days of 58 is the group that toured for 2022’s REALITY: guitarist Matt Kinsey, saxophonist Dustin Laurenzi and drummer Jim White, whose synergy was evident in 2024’s live Resuscitate!. This showed Bill, as he puts it, “that they could handle anything I threw at them,” adding:<br/>“Improv/unpredictability/the unknown is the thing that keeps me motivated to keep making music. It’s all about listening to yourself and others. A lot of the best parts of a recording are the mistakes—making them into strengths, using them as springboards into something human.”<br/>With this in mind, Bill prepared the songs with each player separately. Taking a note from songwriter, fan and friend Jerry DeCicca, he recorded the basic tracks for all but one song in a duo with Jim White. Meanwhile, he rehearsed with Matt, guitar to guitar, while asking Dustin to make horn charts for a few songs. Bill:<br/>“I usually just sing a melody to a horn player or let them try a few takes and go from there. This time I thought, why not get some of the record charted out. There’s always room for spontaneity on top of that. And we did indeed throw some off the cuff stuff on top of the charted horns in a couple cases where they weren’t fully doing what I wanted.<br/>With this record I kept thinking of it as a ‘living room record.’ I’m not talking about fidelity at all here. Living room attitude. Living room vibe. Not too loud, not otherworldly. I asked for the horns to be relaxed like someone on the couch playing, not a blast from heaven or hell.”<br/>For more spontaneity and human color, Bill called up several other players: Richard Bowden on fiddle, whom he’d seen playing with Terry Allen and loved; pianist Pat Thrasher; bassist Chris Vreeland; and trombonist Mike St. Clair. About pedal steel player Bill McCullough, who he knew from Knife in the Water, Bill says this:<br/>“He has a real abstract approach to an abstract instrument—he’s a photographer (shot the front and back cover) and sees the steel in the same way as apertures and f-stops—foreground and mid ground and background—blurry and sharp. That’s how I’ve always seen the steel so it’s exciting to share that. But hobo stew is always the idea—throwing together who I have at hand instead of following a recipe. I’m always learning. I know very little after all these years. I go by gut mostly, but sometimes forget all the possible considerations to consider. The goal of every record at the recording part of the process is to get thrown out of Eden. Every session starts in Eden but you have to get out of there at some point.”<br/>Spotify]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortal Technique (Friday, March 06 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/immortal-technique/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/immortal-technique/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Poison Pen, DJ Static<br/><br/>Friday, March 06 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Facebook<br/>Instagram<br/>YouTube]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenau &amp; Sanborn (Tuesday, March 24 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/rosenau-sanborn/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/rosenau-sanborn/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Joe Westerlund<br/><br/>Tuesday, March 24 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Angels: Passover 2026 Tour (Sunday, May 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-black-angels-passover-2026-tour/lincoln-theatre/raleigh-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-black-angels-passover-2026-tour/lincoln-theatre/raleigh-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Sunday, May 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Lincoln Theatre]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vundabar – ‘Gawk’ 10 Year Anniversary Tour (Wednesday, June 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/vundabar-gawk-10-year-anniversary-tour/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/vundabar-gawk-10-year-anniversary-tour/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Wednesday, June 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Motorco Music Hall]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ritt Momney (Friday, April 24 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/ritt-momney/local-506/chapel-hill-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/ritt-momney/local-506/chapel-hill-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Friday, April 24 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Local 506<br/><br/>Base]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cece Coakley (Sunday, April 26 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/cece-coakley/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/cece-coakley/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, April 26 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foxtide (Thursday, April 30 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/foxtide/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/foxtide/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Thursday, April 30 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>By Storm (Friday, May 15 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/by-storm/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/by-storm/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Lerado Khalil<br/><br/>Friday, May 15 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diggy Graves – The No Vacancy Tour (Friday, August 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 7:30 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/diggy-graves-the-no-vacancy-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/diggy-graves-the-no-vacancy-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Resentvul, Ryan Oakes<br/><br/>Friday, August 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 7:30 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blazers host a Lifetime Celebration for Parthenon Huxley (aka Rick Miller of the Blazers) (Saturday, April 04 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-blazers-host-a-lifetime-celebration-for-parthenon-huxley-aka-rick-miller-of-the-blazers/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-blazers-host-a-lifetime-celebration-for-parthenon-huxley-aka-rick-miller-of-the-blazers/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Saturday, April 04 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superchunk (Saturday, April 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/superchunk-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/superchunk-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Saturday, April 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>“It’s always been the case that everyone is going through something that you may not be aware of,” says the band’s Mac McCaughan. “This is currently more true than ever—but also the case that we are all going through some things together. In the face of that, what good is art and where is happiness found? (Spoiler alert: I don’t know.)”<br/>In seeking an answer, Songs in the Key of Yikes unleashes a sound that is triumphant and bright in the darkness, Majesty Shredding in overdrive. Lead single “Is It Making You Feel Something” sets the tone early with the band—McCaughan, Laura Ballance, Jim Wilbur, and Laura King—building an anthem out of the potential for joy, diving into slop-polluted waters (“now fakes are faking everything / that once made your poor heart sing”) and emerging with a pearl.<br/>“This song is about not second-guessing yourself in the very second-guessable process of writing words and music,” McCaughan explains. “It’s about the legitimate question of ‘who needs this and what is it good for?’ but also about not setting such a high bar for making art that you never get started. ‘Is it making you feel something?’ Ok, that’s a place to start.”<br/>Songs in the Key of Yikes is a signature Superchunk album: visceral and timeless and catchy as hell—a cathartic balm for these oppressive times that will feel even better once we’ve figured our collective shit out.<br/>Website | Facebook]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florence Dore (Thursday, May 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/florence-dore/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/florence-dore/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Davie Circle, Juniper<br/><br/>Thursday, May 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beths (Wednesday, June 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-beths-3/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-beths-3/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Wednesday, June 17 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 22:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evening with Cowboy Junkies (Thursday, June 04 - Doors: 6:30 pm : Show: 7:30 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/an-evening-with-cowboy-junkies-2/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/an-evening-with-cowboy-junkies-2/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Thursday, June 04 - Doors: 6:30 pm : Show: 7:30 pm<br/>Haw River Ballroom<br/><br/>“One of the most unique and enduring bands in alternative rock” – All Music “Margo Timmins’s voice is as melancholy and enchanting as ever” – The New York Times “There’s something that is nearly miraculous about the way Margo Timmins’ beautiful voice fits with those pained lyrics written by her brother Michael Timmins…the result is some truly transformative music.” – The Mercury News Cowboy Junkies will be performing a career-spanning show from The Trinity Session to their recent album, Such Ferocious Beauty! Sometimes revolutions begin quietly. In 1988, Cowboy Junkies proved that there was an audience waiting for something quiet, beautiful and reflective. The Trinity Session was like a whisper that cut through the noise — and it was compelling. It stood out in the midst of the flash and bombast that came to define the late 80’s. The now classic recording combined folk, blues and rock in a way that had never been heard before and went on to sell more than a million copies. Formed in Toronto in 1985 with siblings Michael Timmins on guitar, Margo Timmins on vocals, Peter Timmins on drums, and Michael’s lifelong friend Alan Anton on bass, the band has sparkled over the course of 29 albums. “I’ve known Alan longer than I’ve known Pete,” says Michael. “We were friends before Pete was born.” Unlike most long-lasting groups, Cowboy Junkies have never had a break up or taken a sanity-saving hiatus. There’s an appreciation of each other that keeps them constantly working. “It’s that intimacy and understanding of what each one of us brings to the table,” says Michael.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evening with Cowboy Junkies (Friday, June 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/an-evening-with-cowboy-junkies-3/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/an-evening-with-cowboy-junkies-3/haw-river-ballroom/saxapahaw-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Cat's Cradle Presents<br/><br/>Friday, June 05 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Haw River Ballroom<br/><br/>“One of the most unique and enduring bands in alternative rock” – All Music “Margo Timmins’s voice is as melancholy and enchanting as ever” – The New York Times “There’s something that is nearly miraculous about the way Margo Timmins’ beautiful voice fits with those pained lyrics written by her brother Michael Timmins…the result is some truly transformative music.” – The Mercury News Cowboy Junkies will be performing a career-spanning show from The Trinity Session to their recent album, Such Ferocious Beauty! Sometimes revolutions begin quietly. In 1988, Cowboy Junkies proved that there was an audience waiting for something quiet, beautiful and reflective. The Trinity Session was like a whisper that cut through the noise — and it was compelling. It stood out in the midst of the flash and bombast that came to define the late 80’s. The now classic recording combined folk, blues and rock in a way that had never been heard before and went on to sell more than a million copies. Formed in Toronto in 1985 with siblings Michael Timmins on guitar, Margo Timmins on vocals, Peter Timmins on drums, and Michael’s lifelong friend Alan Anton on bass, the band has sparkled over the course of 29 albums. “I’ve known Alan longer than I’ve known Pete,” says Michael. “We were friends before Pete was born.” Unlike most long-lasting groups, Cowboy Junkies have never had a break up or taken a sanity-saving hiatus. There’s an appreciation of each other that keeps them constantly working. “It’s that intimacy and understanding of what each one of us brings to the table,” says Michael.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nine Lives Flea Market (Sunday, March 08 - Show: 11 am)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-nine-lives-flea-market/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-nine-lives-flea-market/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunday, March 08 - Show: 11 am<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Kingsbury (Tuesday, April 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/caroline-kingsbury/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/caroline-kingsbury/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Bershy<br/><br/>Tuesday, April 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Instagram<br/>Facebook<br/>Spotify]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failure (Sunday, May 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/failure-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/failure-2/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[All Under Heaven<br/><br/>Sunday, May 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yasmin Williams (Saturday, May 30 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/yasmin-williams/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/yasmin-williams/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Seated Show<br/><br/>Saturday, May 30 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 19:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sluice (Friday, May 22 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/sluice/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/sluice/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Peter Horses<br/><br/>Friday, May 22 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 14:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding Places (Thursday, May 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/hiding-places/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/hiding-places/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Thursday, May 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrboro Bluegrass Festival (Saturday, May 23 - Doors: 2 pm : Show: 3 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/carrboro-bluegrass-festival-2/cats-cradle-back-yard/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/carrboro-bluegrass-festival-2/cats-cradle-back-yard/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Saturday, May 23 - Doors: 2 pm : Show: 3 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Yard]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voyage Hot Club, ft. Sam Farthing &amp; Paulus Schaefer (Friday, March 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/voyage-hot-club-ft-sam-farthing-paulus-schaefer/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/voyage-hot-club-ft-sam-farthing-paulus-schaefer/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Carrboro Django Reinhardt Festival<br/><br/>Friday, March 20 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paulus Schaefer (Netherlands) Guitar Workshop (Sunday, March 22 - Doors: 1 pm : Show: 1:30 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/paulus-schaefer-netherlands-guitar-workshop/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/paulus-schaefer-netherlands-guitar-workshop/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Carrboro Django Reinhardt Festival<br/><br/>Sunday, March 22 - Doors: 1 pm : Show: 1:30 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacation Manor (Saturday, February 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/vacation-manor/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/vacation-manor/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Rhineland<br/><br/>Saturday, February 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Since 2016, Vacation Manor combine an artful blend of eloquent lyricism, alternative experimentation, indie rock energy, and unassuming pop appeal. The duo—Nathan Towles [guitar, vocals] and Cole Young [drums]—have earned acclaim from American Songwriter, Atwood, and more. Now, they pull fans deeper into their embrace on their 2025 EP [Nettwerk].<br/>“We value people above all,” adds Nathan. “For us, our music is always better when we can involve our good friends in the process and experience something together. That in and of itself feels like a success for us.”<br/>This community grasped onto the music and never let go. Vacation Manor emerged with the Girl, Say EP highlighted by “Careless” and the breakout “A Toast and a Spirit.” The pair progressed over the course of Everything I Can’t Say Out Loud [2019] and Vacation Manor [2021]. Along the way, they toured alongside Briston Maroney and Night Traveler, in addition to performing at festivals such as Bright Shade Music & Arts Festival. The guys carefully assembled what would become the EP over two years. This time around, songs represented “different landmarks” in their shared and individual experiences. Recording out of a home studio in Virginia, Nathan and Cole self-produced the tracks, nodding to inspirations a la Oasis and The Sundays.<br/>In the end, Vacation Manor’s community will only continue to grow. “With anything we put out, we want to give people language to the things that they’re experiencing too,” Nathan leaves off. “It’s a way for us all to process life.”<br/>Website | Instagram | YouTube | Facebook]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Teeth, Scrape, Minor Stars (Saturday, March 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/slow-teeth-scrape-minor-stars/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/slow-teeth-scrape-minor-stars/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Saturday, March 07 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Still Not Okay Tour (Friday, March 27 - Doors: 6 pm : Show: 7 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/the-still-not-okay-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/the-still-not-okay-tour/cats-cradle/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Rescheduled from Saturday, January 24<br/><br/>Friday, March 27 - Doors: 6 pm : Show: 7 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle<br/><br/>The Still Not Okay Tour Featuring<br/>Turtle Smash: Performing as My Chemical Romance – Playing ‘The Black Parare’ in its entirety + hits<br/>Fake Happy: A Tribute to Paramore<br/>The Dirty Little Rejects: A Tribute to The All-American Rejects<br/>2000s Era Emo After Party – A hit packed super set featuring members from all bands.<br/>Website]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Smart + Willy Tea Taylor (Thursday, April 09 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/jordan-smart-willy-tea-taylor/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/jordan-smart-willy-tea-taylor/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a seated show<br/><br/>Thursday, April 09 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Honey (Thursday, April 23 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/easy-honey/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/easy-honey/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Thursday, April 23 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Party (Friday, April 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/wild-party-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/wild-party-2/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretoria<br/><br/>Friday, April 10 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Website<br/>Instagram<br/>Facebook<br/>YouTube<br/>TikTok]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model/Actriz (Wednesday, March 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/model-actriz/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/model-actriz/motorco-music-hall/durham-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Moved to Motorco from Cat's Cradle Back Room<br/><br/>Wednesday, March 25 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Motorco Music Hall]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paulus Schaefer and Friends (Saturday, March 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm)</title>
      <link>https://catscradle.com/event/paulus-schaefer-and-friends/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</link>
      <guid>https://catscradle.com/event/paulus-schaefer-and-friends/cats-cradle-back-room/carrboro-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Carrboro Django Reinhardt Festival<br/><br/>Saturday, March 21 - Doors: 7 pm : Show: 8 pm<br/>Cat’s Cradle Back Room]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://catscradle.com/wp-content/plugins/cookie-law-info/lite/frontend/images/revisit.svg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
